RG 005:034, Office of the Governor: John Dempsey (1961-1971)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 13. Articles and Statements by Gov. Dempsey, 1961-1970
  - Leukemia - Message Taped by WTIC for use on WABC New York, 1963 October 9 (Box A-464)
  - Marianapolis Preparatory School, Guest Editorial in the Golden Knight, 1962 March 9 (Box A-464)
  - Guest Editorial "Mayor and Manager" Magazine (New York, N.Y.), 1962 February (Box A-464)
  - Statement by Governor Dempsey on Middle East Crisis, 1967 June (Box A-464)
  - Milford Citizen Article (for Affairs of State Column), 1962 September 11 (Box A-464)
  - Milford Reporter (Article for 325th Anniversary of the City of Milford mailed on 1964 May 4) (Box A-464)
  - Article for National Herald - Holiday Greetings 1962 (Box A-464)
  - The Nationalist "Irish Newspaper" Article by Keith Schonrock (Box A-464)
  - Naugatuck Valley Industrial Council (Signing of Contract for Training High School Students), 1966 June 7 (Box A-464)
  - New Britain Herald - Article for 1963 Automobile Edition, 1963 January, 1964, 1965 (Box A-464)
  - New Britain Herald - Article to be used in Education Section, 1963 August 15, 1964 August (Box A-464)
  - New Britain Herald (Box A-464)
  - New England Homestead Letter re: Eastern States Exposition, 1962 July 30 (Box A-464)
  - New England Park Association Newsletter (Box A-464)
  - New Era, Deep River (Box A-464)
  - TV-Radio Tape - New Haven Railroad - re: Sec. Connors' Letter, 1966 March 3 (Box A-464)
  - New Haven Register - 4th of July Highway Safety Message, 1965 June 24 (Box A-464)
  - New Haven Register - Letter for World's Fair Supplement, 1964 April 15 (Box A-464)
  - Newspapers - Miscellaneous Messages (Box A-464)
  - Newspaper Week - Statement from Governor to New Haven Register, 1961 October 13 (Box A-464)
  - New York Stock Exchange Taped Message by Governor Dempsey, 1966 March 21 (Box A-464)
  - Articles Norwich Bulletin (Box A-464)
  - Radio Stations - Taped Messages Miscellaneous (Box A-464)
  - Television Program "Public Office" WNAW - Channel 5 New York (Box A-464)
  - Statement Given Rockville Journal re: Todd Division of Burroughs Corp., 1962 December 20 (Box A-464)
  - Scouting Magazine, 1965 (Box A-464)
  - Scouting Magazine December, 1964 (Box A-464)
  - Search Light Program, Channel 4,New York, 1964 May 24 (Box A-464)
  - Signal 30 Message, Channel 18, 1961 December 28 (Box A-464)
  - Article for Stamford JCees Commentator, 1963 November 13 (Box A-464)
  - Sunday Herald - Article for Better Business Climate Edition (Mailed 1963 August 5) (Box A-464)
  - Sunday Herald Article, 1962 April (Box A-464)
  - Articles on the Economy for the Sunday Herald, 1961 March 16 (Box A-464)
  - Telephone Company Bulletin Article, 1962 September (Box A-464)
  - United Press - International Statement re: National GOP Conference (Box A-464)
  - United Press International (Box A-464)
  - United Press International - Statement on Anti-Communism Courses; Public Schools (Box A-464)
  - UPI - Queries re: Vietnam Situation, 1964 August 6 (Box A-464)
  - United Press International - Statement on Industry, 1962 December 28 (Box A-464)
  - University of Conn. - Articles on Education for Conn. Daily Campus, 1962 October 11 (Box A-464)
  - UPI - Statement by Governor on Record of 1963 General Assembly, 1963 June 7 (Box A-464)
  - WBIS Station - Bristol, Taped for Opening of New Studio, 1967 February 28 (Box A-464)
  - WBZ TV Boston, Higher Education Documentary, 1967 March 3 (Box A-464)
  - WCCC Taped Message for Special Program in Tribute to Thomas Quirk and Hugh Greer, 1963 January 20 (Box A-464)
  - WCCC - Taped Message of Congratulations 15th Anniversary, Taped, 1962 October 23 (Box A-464)
  - 1961 Year End Message Taped for WCCC and WINF (Box A-464)
  - WDEE - Radio Station - Hamden (Box A-464)
  - WDRC - Taped Message for Teen-Age March against Leukemia, 1963 May, 1964 April (Box A-464)
  - WDRC - 40th Anniversary Message, 1962 September 28 (Box A-464)
  - WHAY - Interview, Taped, 1962 August 27 (Box A-464)
  - WNHB Channel 30 Taping of St. Patrick, Irish-American Home Society, 1967 March 9 (Box A-464)
  - WHNC - Taped Message on Civil Defense, 1966 August 16 (Box A-464)
  - WNHC - TV - Taped Message re: Alfred P. Sloan Award, 1966 May 20 (Box A-464)
  - WHNC - TV - Taped Message by Gov. Dempsey for the 14th Anniversary (Taped), 1961 October 20 (Box A-464)
  - WICH - Norwich, Establishment of Industrial Park, 1966 September 2 (Box A-464)
  - Station WILL (Willimantic), 1961 September 20 (Box A-464)
  - WINY, Putnam, One Minute Tape for October 31, 1966, 1966 October 31 (Box A-464)
  - WNEW -TV (New York) Transcript of Program, Taped, 1965 March 26 (Box A-464)
  - Station WNLC - Taped Christmas Message), 1966 December 20 (Box A-464)
  - WOR (New York), 1965 October 25 (Box A-464)
  - Radio Station WOWW - Naugatuck (Taped Message for the First Day of Broadcast), 1961 February 25 (Box A-464)
  - Station WPOP - 3 Safety Messages Taped by Governor, 1961 October 26 (Box A-464)
  - Radio Station WSCH - Message, Taped, 1962 August 30 (Box A-464)
  - Radio Station WSOR, Windsor, Message on First Day of Broadcast (Box A-464)
  - WTIC Debate, Sunday, 1966 October 30 (Box A-464)
  - WTIC - Statement of Governor Dempsey Taped from L.A., Calif. (National Governors' Conference), 1966 July 6 (Box A-464)
  - WTIC - Taped, for CD Test, 1966 June 21 (Box A-464)
  - WTIC - Taped Message for 40th Anniversary, Taped, 1965 February 5 (Box A-464)
  - WTIC - Taping of Message for Community Chest, 1963 September 19 (Box A-464)
  - WTIC - Taped Message (Signing of Bill re: Labeling of Non-Prescription Medicines Containing a Narcotic) for use 1963 June 5 (Box A-464)
  - Editorial - Waterbury Republican - Waterbury American, St. Patrick's Day, 1961 (Box A-464)
  - Waterbury Republican - Article for Editorial Page, 1962 September 21 (Box A-464)
  - Windham County Observer - Putnam Patriot, Article in Paper, 1963 January 9 (Box A-464)
  - Windsor Police Advisories (Taped Program for Station WSOR Windsor, Taped, 1962 March 19 (Box A-464)
  - The Official Grapevine (Box A-464)
  - Waterbury Republican - Article for Editorial Page, 1962 September (Box A-464)
  - WCBS "Opinion of the Air" NY, 1962 April 17 (Box A-464)
- Series 14. Press Releases, 1962-1970
  Chronological.
  - 1962 January-1967 September (Box A-465)
  - 1967 October-1968 September (Box A-466)
  - 1968 October-1969 July (Box A-467)
  - 1969 August-1970 February (Box A-468)
  - 1970 March-1970 December (Box A-469)
- Series 15. Press Department Files, 1955-1970
  Includes press clippings, releases, documents and a little correspondence.
  No separate container listings.
  - 1955-1965 (Box A-470 - A-475)
  - 1966-1968 (Box A-476 - A-482)
  - 1969 (Box A-482 - A-485)
  - 1970 (Box A-486 - A-488)
  - Constitutional Convention, 1965 (Box A-488)
  - Articles about Gov. Dempsey (Box A-489)
  - General Assembly material, 1957-1968 (Box A-490 - A-496)
  - Material on teen-age drinking (Box A-496)
  - Photographs (Box A-407 - A-500)
    See listing at History and Genealogy reference desk.
  - Campaign material, 1962-1966 (Box A-501 - A-505)
  - Scrapbook of clippings, 1966 (Box A-506)
- Series 16. Highway Safety Files, 1961-1967
  Mostly reference material by subject or title.
  - Records (Box A-507)
- Series 17. John Dempsey records as Lieutenant Governor, 1958-1960
  Fragmentary and unarranged.
  - Records (Box A-508)
- Series 18. John Dempsey records as Executive Aide to Gov. Ribicoff and as Mayor of Putnam, 1955-1957
  Mostly alphabetical by correspondent.
  - Records (Box A-509)
- Series 19. Robert J. Beckwith records, Aide to Gov. Dempsey, 1961-1965
  By subject or correspondent.
  - Records (Box A-510)
- Series 20. Commission on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1961-1965
  (See also Subject Files, Box A-253)
  - Records (Box A-511)